with the launch of universes Beyond
Assassin's Creed we're getting a brand
new booster pack a Beyond booster on a
recent stream Wizards have recently
confirmed some more details around the
pack so I'm going to cover everything
you need to know about them firstly why
create Beyond boosters the Assassin's
Creed expansion has been mentioned to be
around 100 cards in size which the
Wizard's team mention is clearly too
large for a secret layer release but not
large enough to design four Commander
decks around them not to mention the
lack of four distinct factions or a
large roster of well-known characters
and this is where the Beyond booster was
born the Beyond booster sits somewhere
between epilog boosters and play
boosters epilog boosters came with five
cards in total no Commons one to three
rares or mythics and the remainder of
the pack being uncommons and play
boosters came with 14 playable cards in
total 67 of them being Commons three
uncommons and up to four rares and
mythics now Beyond boosters come with
seven playable cards in total three
uncommons a land that has a chance to be
replaced with a Scene Card more and that
in a second one rare or Mythic a foil
wild card that can be of any Rarity and
last but not least a fun booster variant
card that can also be of any Rarity
booster fun cards are the name given to
the cards with a special frame treatment
these include extend arts borderless art
showcase cards and retro frames we've
previously seen scen cards in The Lord
of the Ring set they are simply just a
group of cards with alternative art
where you can combine their artwork to
form a larger picture just like
collector boosters and the now retired
set boosters Beyond boosters are not
draftable they are however designed with
60 card formats in mind in this case
specifically modern just just like the
Lord of the Ring set the Assassin's
Creed set will be modern legal the
Wizards team mentioned on the stream
that the goal of these Beyond boosters
is to provide Evergreen Staples so it
sounds like we're getting a mini modern
Horizon set just before the release of
modern Horizons 3 the Wizards team also
mentioned that they took on board the
wellth thought out and constructive
criticism that came out after the launch
of March of the machine the aftermath
however at this point the Beyond
boosters had already been designed and
the team was super bullish on epilog
boosters being well received so as we
already know the Beyond boosters now
contain seven cards instead of five the
Wizards team did mention they took on
board feedback around pricing but
haven't confirmed what they've actioned
from that we'll likely hear something
around May or June when Distributors
contact
stores so what do we think of Beyond
boosters so far I'll be sure to keep you
all updated as the news drops and as
always be sure to like the video If you
learned something and subscribe if you
don't want Etso to come and get you
thanks for watching and I'll see you in
the next one